(Leonard:)...most people don't sort their breakfast
cereal numerically by fiber content.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, but I think
we've both found that helpful at times.
- Come on, we should go.
- Hang on.
- What are you doing?
- I'm straightening up.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, this is not your home.
(Sheldon:)This is not anyone's home.
This is a swirling vortex of entropy.
(Leonard:)When the transvestite lived here,
you didn't care how he kept the place.
(Sheldon:)Because it was immaculate.
(Sheldon:)I mean, you open that man's closet...
(Sheldon:)...it was left to right, evening gowns,
cocktail dresses and his police uniforms.
- What were you doing in his closet?
- I helped him run some cable for a webcam.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, hey, Penny.
(Leonard:)This just arrived.
Brought this up. Just now.
Great. Was it hard getting up the stairs?
(Leonard:)- No.
- No?
- No.
(Leonard:)- We'll get out of your hair.
- Okay, great.
(Penny:)Thank you again.